I've got a bit of
news that might cheer you up.
Best thing I've had in
a long while.
I've got an informant
who runs a pub
and there's a dealer
who goes in here,
serves him a bit of
knocked off booze and that.
And he says he was
involved in a job
and him and his little crew
got off with it Scott free.
Five years ago.
In Whitfield.
Every Thursday about three-ish
he swings by the pub,
does his little bit of
business, he's got a Van.
Only problem is, he's
got moody number plates
so I couldn't get his
home address.
Where's the pub?
Harry, I'm gonna be
honest with you mate,
you don't look up to it.
Where's the pub?
Cheers, mo.
God bless ya.
Thank you.
What can I get ya?
A lager pint.
We disagree.
That's the main thing, it
means more money, a grand.
Like to sort it out.
Got to shift it, haven't I, so..
Yeah and keep
it discrete, you know?
They're putting the pressure.
If he finds out you're doing it
and they get to us through you.
Go, drive!
Fucking go!
Come on!
Drive the fucking car.
- Fucking drive!
- Go!
Come on!
Go, fucking go!
Probably gonna go cry somewhere.
He's going to start crying.
Come on, bring him back here
and cut his fucking cock off.
Bring him back in, I
ain't joking.
Why?
What'd ya think?
What's so difficult?
Yeah what's the problem with it?
You're going to shoot him.
Both of them, in the
head, on the roof, now.
Come on.
If you don't shoot him,
I'll stab you in the
fucking face!
All right?
Gotta get him from the basement.
Get on the roof now.
They need to be dead.
Come on, go, go!
Come on, go!
Come on, get in the fucking car!
This is my fucking house.
When they've all came to my
fucking manor.
Hold the gun up, and point it
in their fucking heads.
Show what happens when they
walk into my fucking house.
You two on your knees.
You an all.
I said on your knees.
Do it!
I said fucking do it!
Fucking do it or I'll
stab you right now.
Fucking do it!
Or I'll stab you if you
don't fucking do it!
Now!
Your mates, where
have they gone?
Where are they?
The countryside.
Why?
Picking up a delivery.
Drugs?
When?
A couple of days.
Write it down.
Come on, come on!
Write down the address.
That's my pen.
Sorry.
Who are you?
They were my life.
I knew I'd see you again.
I waited, I hoped, I prayed,
I would see you all again.
I need a doctor.
What's with the gun?
Don't get up.
Doesn't suit ya.
Please don't get up.
We're going to find ya,
we're going to kill ya.
Just like we killed
those two bitches!
- Oh.
- Sorry.
I'm, I'm really hungry.
Don't worry about it.
I've got the munchies too.
That's beautiful.
Looks really peaceful.
I used to go there
with my husband.
Well when he was alive.
It's supposed to be sunny there
tomorrow, according to my phone.
Was he a good husband?
Yeah.
He was funny too.
I'm going to heat this up.
I'm so sorry.
It's for your throat.
You know yesterday, we...
We'd have continued
that I don't...
I understand.
- Good book?
- Yeah.
"The count of monte cristo."
It was a present from my wife.
Are you still married?
We're separated.
"It is necessary to have
wished for death in order
to know how good it is to live."
The French, they have a
way with words, don't they?
And food.
Do you know what they
call an orgasm?
La petit morte.
It means small death.
Can I ask you something?
Yeah, of course.
I need to take tomorrow off.
Yeah, okay.
No!
Run.
Fucking run!
Hurry up!
Fuck you, fuck, fuck!
That's $4.99 please.
Haven't taken the pills.
What the fuck is this?
Where is he?
You're lucky.
Yeah.
Give yourself a shot
every four hours.
For the pain, very
strong opiates.
Careful with them.
No more than three a day.
No answer.
Check next door.
That fat cunt took my knife.
I want it back.
You grab his legs and
mind the blood.
You okay?
Yeah, I've twisted my shoulder.
Ahh, thank you.
How was your day off?
Get a lot done?
Yeah.
Hey.
So, you'll close up, yeah?
We're going to be closed
for a couple of days.
Oh, guess you know that.
Yeah, well, obviously
you know that.
I can't speak properly.
Um.
I'm going to the seaside.
I rented myself a little place.
It's my birthday.
I'm getting old.
It's better than the
alternative.
Oh.
Yeah, well.
If you wanted
to come visit, stay,
it's um,
it's the address and the phone.
It'll be nice to see you.
Happy birthday, Emma.
Hello, Harry.
You'd been better
forgetting about us.
Well, you think you
can just walk away, huh?
Where's my knife?
Eh?
Where's my fucking knife?
There shoot him!
Shoot him!
There, shoot him!
Hold him, fucking hold
him straight! Hold him!
Fucking bit me.
This is the
Henderson detective agency.
Please leave a message
after the tone.
Fuck!
This is the
Henderson detective agency.
Please leave a message
after the tone.
Stockers farm, ricksmansworth.
He's fucking lying.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Fucking snitch.
Here he is.
What you doing?
Here, here. Sit.
You want some biscuits?
I think I've got some in the ca.
What happened to you?
I suggest you go to a hospital.
I'm just a vet.
How are my horses?
They only stable five now.
Between here and the practice,
I just couldn't keep up.
Sorry.
Everyone asks about you.
Where have you been?
All these years.
I've found them.
All of them.
I need you to leave me
alone for a few days.
Don't tell anyone I'm here.
Don't come and see me.
You're sure they're coming?
I just killed three of them.
We used to walk around
here when she was pregnant.
You must get ready.
I'm scared.
Take it.
Where is he?
Come on!
Where the fuck is he?
Check upstairs.
Waste of time. He's not here.
Stay here.
It's over.
It's not.
Go home.